

Hola, soy Alex — Soy **diseñador de producto** con conocimientos de **desarrollo front-end**. Estoy particularmente interesado en la **experiencia del usuario, la usabilidad y la investigación**, así como sus aplicaciones para mejorar la vida de las personas. Mi lengua materna es el **español** y hablo **inglés** con fluidez.

# **Experiencia**

# Diseñador de producto — Emprendimiento

#### **EventNest**

Oct 2024 — Hoy España — Remoto

I am working on the creation of a **marketplace** that helps event organizers and promoters find the services they need to develop their activities. The project is currently in its initial phase, where I am conducting the necessary research to define the **MVP** (Minimum Viable Product) to begin working on.

## Diseñador de producto — Emprendimiento

#### Geomites

Mar 2023 — Hoy España — Remoto

I lead the UX and UI design of this project, where we are designing and developing a **mobile video**game for iOS and Android platforms in an agile environment.

## Diseñador de producto — Freelance

Abr 2022 — Hoy España — Remoto

I work as a product designer for different companies and sectors. My main freelance activities include designing and developing **company websites**, designing **corporate documents**, and participating in the **design process** of various products or services.

# Responsable de marketing — Contratado

#### Promam

Jul 2017 — Sep 2021 España — In situ

I was responsible for marketing and design tasks, managing the design and development of the **company's website** and led **SEO** positioning campaigns. I spearheaded marketing campaigns on social media and organized and developed the design of various products necessary for the company's operations, including **catalogs, advertisements, and documents**. I also collaborated with stakeholders to organize the **marketing and sales strategy**.

## Educación

# Google & Coursera, Interaction Design Foundation

2021 - Present

Pensamiento de diseño: La guía definitiva, Experiencia del usuario: Guía para principiantes, Fundamentos de la experiencia de usuario, Investigación de usuarios, Psicología Gestalt, Interacción persona-ordenador, Diseño para el siglo XXI, Diseño emocional, Visualización de la información, Experiencia de usuario, Diseño visual, Patrones de diseño.

## **Universidad Rey Juan Carlos**

Grado en Marketing

2011 - 2016

### **Habilidades**

Investigación UX, Diseño UX, Diseño UI, Wireframing, Prototipado, Resolución de problemas, Comunicación, Sistemas de diseño, Usabilidad.

## Herramientas

Sketch, Figma, Adobe Creative suite, Framer, Webflow, Wordpress, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Axure, Asana, Jira, ChatGPT, Midjourney, NotebookLM

#### Contacto

<u>alejandromorenomartin.com</u> +34 618110583 alejandromorenomartin1990@gmail.com